原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     苏小黛  桃小兔  月月  TheWalkingNerd
翻译     一只虾  小酸奶  Lynn_宁  Silence
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     知之
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
双峰
第三季第四集
中了多少大奖
How many jackpots?
目前有29次头奖
So far, 29 mega jackpots.
我死定了
I'm dead.
大奖先生  大奖先生
Mr. Jackpots! Mr. Jackpots!
告诉我选哪台
Tell me which one.
30次了
Now 30.
谢谢你  大奖先生
Thank you, Mr. Jackpots!
谢谢  谢谢你  大奖先生
Thank you! Thank you, Mr. Jackpots.
谢谢  太谢谢你了
Thank you. Thank you so much.
谢谢  谢谢  谢谢
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
道吉
Dougie!
道吉  是你吗
Dougie, is that you?
我是比尔·谢克  联合化工的
It's Bill Shaker, Allied Chemicals.
怎么  你出来晃晃吗
What, are you taking a walk on the wild side?
比尔·谢克
Bill Shaker.
道吉·琼斯
Dougie Jones.
对  我是比尔·谢克  你是道吉·琼斯
Yes. I'm Bill Shaker, and you're Dougie Jones.
天  道吉  我能说你看起来像百万富翁吗
Man, Dougie, can I say, you look like a million bucks.
怎么回事  减肥了吗  换了发型
What is it, the diet? New haircut?
抱歉  我也很饿
I'm sorry. I'm really hungry.
我早上在家吃了饭  到现在还没吃过东西
I haven't eaten since breakfast at home.
家
Home.
抱歉  我没明白  道吉
Sorry. I don't get it, Dougie.
你想回家吗  道吉
You want to go home, Dougie?
是吗
Is that right?
我觉得他想回家
I think he wants to go home.
回家
Home.
你想知道家在哪  是吗
Where is your home? Is that right?
他知道他家在哪
He knows where his home is.
那他家在哪
Well, where is his home?
家在哪
Where home?
我的天  在兰斯洛特法院
Oh, my God. Lancelot Court.
你家大门是红色的
Your house has the red door.
我每次都是那样找到你家的
That's how I always find it.
在梅林家的市场附近
Near Merlin's Market.
离这里不远
It's not far from here.
离这里远
Far from here.
不  离这里不远
No, not far from here.
打车可能六块至八块吧
It's maybe a $6 or $8 cab ride.
打车
Cab ride.
你肯定遇到了什么事  是吗  道吉
Something must have happened, right, Dougie?
外面门口有一整排的出租车
There's a whole line of cabs right out front.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
他没事吧
Is he okay?
很高兴见到你  道吉
It was good to see you, Dougie!
天  希望他没事
Gee, I hope he's okay.
我觉得他不太好
I don't think he's okay.
他在这里
He's here!
他要走了
He's leaving!
不好意思  先生
Excuse me? Sir?
不好意思  请留步  先生
Excuse me. Excuse me. Sir? Hi.Hi.
请你跟我来一下好吗
Can you, uh, please come with me?
我们走这边
We'll go this way.
来吧
Come on.
你赢的钱都不拿可不能走
You weren't going to leave without your winnings,
对吧  先生
were you, sir?
先生
Sir?
我们能帮你做些什么吗
Is there anything we can do to help?
找人帮忙
Call for help.
找谁
Call who?
谁
Who?
我们当然愿意帮助你
Well, we'd certainly like to help you.
要不要开个房间  有好吃的好喝的
Would you like a room? Good meal? A drink?
再找人陪陪你
A little companionship?
算我们的
On the house.
就当我们是
Think of us as
离开家之外的另一个家吧
a home away from home.
家
Home.
你住在这附近吗
And do you live around here?
你家在哪
Where is your home?
兰斯洛特法院  打车
Lancelot Court. Cab ride.
不不  不打车
Oh, no, no, no. No cabs.
你叫什么  先生
What's your name, sir?
道吉·琼斯
Dougie Jones.
为琼斯先生准备一辆豪车
Limo for Mr. Jones.
史密斯  请开一辆豪车出来
Smithie, bring a limo around front, please.
但你得答应我一件事
But you have to promise me something.
你要再回来试试运气
You'll come back and try your luck with us again...
尽早  什么时候都行
soon, anytime...
白天或是晚上都行
day or night.
或是晚上
Or night.
对
That's right.
我们在看着你
We're watching you,
琼斯...  先生
Mr....Jones.
我们在兰斯洛特短街上
We're on Lancelot Court.
你不知道自己住在哪儿吗
You don't know your address?
只知道门是红色的吗
Just a red door?
红色的门
Red door.
问题是
The thing is, though,
晚上很难看清颜色
it's hard to see the color at night.
红色
Red.
不是
No.
那是黑色的
That's black.
我刚才说了  晚上真的很难
Like I was saying, it-it's real tough
看清楚颜色  所以...
to see the color at night, so...
就在那儿
There it is.
你的家门就在那边  琼斯先生
There's your door right there, Mr. Jones.
琼斯先生  琼斯先生
Mr. Jones? Mr. Jones?
琼斯先生
Mr. Jones.
好吧
All right.
好吧  我在这儿陪着你
All right. I'll wait right here with you.
该死
Damn.
你这样吓到我了
Those things spook me.
道吉
Dougie?
是你吗
Is that you?
道吉
Dougie!
你去哪儿了
Where have you been?
-这是什么  -夫人...
- What is this? - Ma'am...
他是银色野马的客人
h-he was a guest at the Silver Mustang,
他一个人去的  老板叫我送他回家
on his own, and I was asked to bring him home.
我走了
I'll be going now.
一句话都没说就消失了三天
Three days without a word?
你没去上班
You don't show up at work,
也没去桑尼·吉姆的生日会
and you miss Sonny Jim's birthday.
你怎么能这样
How could you?
给我进屋去
Get inside.
你都干什么去了
What have you been doing?
为什么不打电话给我
Why didn't you call me?
你哪儿搞的黑西装
Where'd you get that black suit...
还有这发型  道吉
and that haircut, Dougie?
袋子里是什么
What's in this bag?
道吉
Dougie?
Dougie.
道吉  这里面...
Dougie, there's...
这里面有好几万美元
there's thousands and thousands of dollars here.
你从哪儿弄来的
Where did you get this?
是从银色野马那儿弄的吗
Did you get this at the Silver Mustang?
道吉
Dougie!
别跟我说你中了头奖
Don't tell me you hit the jackpot.
头奖先生
Mr. Jackpots.
是你赢的
You won it?
道吉
Dougie?
这些钱足够付给他们了
Well, there's--there's enough here to pay them back.
那个...  你可以...
The-- You could--
我们可以...
We could...
这是我这辈子最美妙  最可怕的一天了
This is the most wonderful... horrible day of my life.
我这辈子
Of my life.
是的
Yes.
我给你做个三明治
I'm gonna fix you a sandwich,
然后我再给你拿块
and then I'm gonna get you a piece
桑尼·吉姆的巧克力蛋糕
of Sonny Jim's chocolate cake,
我们特意为你留的
'cause we saved a piece for you.
好吗
Okay?
道吉
Oh, Dougie.
你回家我真是太高兴了  道吉
I'm so glad you're home, Dougie.
家
Home.
秘书长一会儿就来会见你
The chief of staff will be with you in a moment.
她在哪儿
Where is she?
在开会  马上就结束了
In a meeting. She's just finishing up.
好的  比尔
Okay, Bill.
-玛莎最近好吗  -挺好的
- How's Martha? - Oh, she's fine.
谢谢你  戈登
Thank you, Gordon.
她和保罗的那码事解决了吗
She ever fix that thing with Paul?
解决了  解决了
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes.
谢谢你还记得
Good of you to remember.
保罗现在在北极了
Paul is now in the North Pole.
真好
Well, there you go.
请坐吧
Please, have a seat.
谢谢你  比尔
Thank you, Bill.
丹妮斯
Denise.
戈登
Gordon.
谢谢你过来  有什么情况吗
Thank you for coming in. What have you got?
是库柏
It's Cooper.
我们找到他了
We found him.
在哪里
Where?
南达科他州  丹妮斯
South Dakota, Denise.
他在南达科他州的一个联邦监狱里
He's in a federal prison in South Dakota.
我们明天就去见他
We're going out to see him tomorrow.
我听说了
I heard.
是吗  怎样
Yes? How's that?
你要带普雷斯顿探员和你一起去吗
You're taking Agent Preston with you?
没错
Yes.
不是吧  戈登
Really, Gordon?
你这是什么意思  丹妮斯
What are you getting at, Denise?
我了解你  戈登
Well, I know your profile, Gordon.
漂亮的女探员  不到30岁
Beautiful agent, barely 30.
我作风很老派的  丹妮斯  你心里清楚
I'm old-school, Denise. You know that.
在你变成丹妮斯之前
Before you were Denise,
那时你还是丹尼斯  而我是你的上司
when you were Dennis and I was your boss,
我让你去缉毒局卧底的时候
when I had you working undercover at the DEA,
你有时真是又迷糊又狂野
you were a confused and wild thing sometimes.
我手里关于你的黑料足以填平大峡谷了
I had enough dirt on you to fill the Grand Canyon,
但我从来没有利用过那些黑料
and I never used a spoonful
因为你当时和如今都是个好探员
because you were and are a great agent.
你变成丹妮斯的时候
And when you became Denise,
我放话给你那些同事  那些跳梁小丑
I told all of your colleagues, those clown comics,
要么接受你  要么就去死
to fix their hearts or die.
没错  就像我之前多次说过的那样  戈登
Yes, and as I've said many times before, Gordon,
我永远也报答不完你对我的恩情
I can never repay you enough for that kindness.
塔米·普雷斯顿探员有这个能力  丹妮斯
Agent Tammy Preston has the stuff, Denise.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
我现在是以一个女人的身份在讲话
I'm speaking more as a woman now
而不是整个联邦调查局的秘书长
than as the chief of staff of the entire federal Bureau of Investigation.
你有时会不会很享受
Don't you just love sometimes saying
像那样一口气说出
"Federal Bureau of Investigation"
"联邦调查局"
like that all at once?
不省略一个字
Unabbreviated?
这样真是让我兴奋极了
It just gives me such a thrill.
是很让人兴奋  丹妮斯
It is thrilling, Denise.
塔米她...
And Tammy...
塔米真是太漂亮了
Tammy is so beautiful.
联邦调查局里容得下
There's room in this Federal Bureau of Investigation
不止一个漂亮女人
for more than one beautiful woman.
戈登
Oh, Gordon.
这话真是太甜了
That is so sweet.
平时我是不能像这样思考的
You know, normally, I can't think like this.
在这个工作上我得摒弃那些念头  作风铁腕
I have to forgo all that and grow balls of steel to do this job,
而那真的是...很烦人
and it's--it's a bitch,
我告诉你有时候真的是的
let me tell you, sometimes--
更别提我体内咆哮着的荷尔蒙
not to mention the screaming hormones.
我明白  抱歉  戈登
I know. I'm sorry, Gordon.
我明白
I know.
戈登  我信任你
Gordon, I trust you.
你是知道的
You know that.
我觉得你是在追查某件大事
And I believe you're on the trail of something big.
大事
Big.
艾伯特会和你一起去吗
Will Albert be with you?
鸟儿会飞吗
Do birds fly?
祝你好运
Good luck.
收到  好伙计
Ten-four, good buddy.
谢谢你  比尔
Thank you, Bill.
请跟我来
Please come along.
双峰镇警察局
这和恒温器有关
Well, it has to do with the thermostat.
没人的时候
It doesn't actually tell you what's going on
这玩意没法告诉你发生了什么事
when no one's here.
大部分时候  我们没有犯人
Uh, mostly, we don't have prisoners,
但就算我们有
but even if we did,
他们甚至都看不见这个恒温器
they couldn't even see the thermostat.
所以我最近找了个人看着炉子
So I had a man out here recently to look at the furnace,
结果啊  杜鲁门警长
and, Sheriff Truman,
他也不肯回答我
he wouldn't answer any of my questions
这里无人时是什么情形
about what happens when no one's here.
我们来的早  暖气是开着的
We come in early, and the heat is still on.
如果我们来的更早呢
What if we came in even earlier?
暖气也会是开着的吗
Would the heat still be on then?
你在很大声的河流边吗  杜鲁门警长
Are you next to a loud stream, Sheriff Truman?
你声音断断续续的
You're breaking up.
你还在钓鱼吗
Are you still fishing?
你旁边河流是不是很吵
Are you next to a really loud stream?
你断断续续的  警长
You're breaking up, Sheriff.
希望等你回到办公室
Well, I-I hope we can get this sorted out
我们能把这事搞清楚
when you get back to the office,
但现在这里很舒适
but right now, it's very comfortable in here.
我得挂了  杜鲁门警长  因为现在
I have to go, Sheriff Truman, because there are some people
有人从前门进来了
coming in through the front door.
露西  露西
Lucy. Lucy.
你刚刚又在和她讲电话  对吧
You were on the phone with her again, weren't you?
安迪  很抱歉  我们信号中断了
Andy, I'm sorry. We lost connection.
我总不能在停车场里站一整晚吧
I couldn't stand out in the parking lot all night.
我恨手机
I hate cellular phones.
这怎么可能
How is this possible?
露西  把电话挂了
Lucy, hang up the phone.
但你在山上
But you're in the mountains...
钓鱼啊
fishing!
乖乖
Oh, punky.
Punky.
1171  1507
Eleven seventy-one. Fifteen oh-seven.
Ten-four.
610  1007
Six ten. Ten oh-seven.
收到
Copy that.
你好  警长
Oh, hi, Sheriff.
晚上好  玛吉
Evening, Maggie.
今晚有什么状况
What's going on tonight?
挺平静的
Kind of quiet.
一起家庭纠纷  两件酒后闹事  一个酒驾
A domestic, two D&Ds, and a DUI.
那个是我办的
I booked that one.
他酒测值0.25
Dude blew a .250.
连鼻子都找不到了  更别说要摸鼻子
Could not even find his nose, let alone touch it.
还有件很糟糕的
Oh, and it was terrible.
有个男孩在高中药物过量
A boy OD'd at the high school--
丹尼斯·克雷格
Dennis Craig.
安迪接的案子
Andy took the case.
他和家长谈过了
He spoke with the parents.
小丹尼·克雷格
Little Denny Craig.
放学钟声响了
When the bell rang,
他却再也没离开他书桌
he never got up from his desk.
霍克人呢
Where's Hawk?
他在会议室
He's in the conference room.
各位
Gents.
博比
Bobby.
又一起明显药物过量
Another apparent OD--
小丹尼·克雷格
little Denny Craig,
虽然我还没看验尸报告
although I haven't seen the autopsy report.
我猜
I'm guessing it was...
又是中国来的特制药物
Chinese designer drugs again.
你的监控摄像有录到什么吗
Anything on your surveillance cameras?
各种鹿啊
Uh, elk, deer,
浣熊  松鼠
raccoon, squirrel,
还有只熊
and a bear.
如果他们是从加拿大来到这里的
If they're coming down from Canada in our area,
我应该会看到
I would've seen them.
-每条路线都有我守着  -已知的路线
- I got every trail covered. - Every known trail.
对
Right.
弗兰克  我尿很急
Frank, I got to take a leak so bad,
都快满到嘴里了
my back teeth are floatin'.
回头会议室见
Meet you in the conference room.
太好了  长官
Good deal, sir.
手机
Cell phones...
代表它们能随身携带
that means they're mobile, punky.
警长可能在移动中
The sheriff can be moving.
不像你的电话
It's not like your phone.
他说话的同时可能正在移动
He can be moving and even driving
甚至在开车
while he's talking.
露西
Lucy...
你工作各方面
you're so good at your job
都非常能干
in every other way.
我就不明白为什么这情况
I just don't understand how this keeps happening...
老是发生
over and over again.
我也不明白  安迪
I don't understand it either, Andy.
你休息一下
You collect yourself.
我要去见杜鲁门警长
I've got to go see Sheriff Truman.
我知道她这人有点奇怪
I know she seems like a strange one,
但她提供的信息都是正确的
but her information has always been spot-on.
那么
So...
玛格丽特说
Margaret says
有样跟戴尔·库柏特工有关的东西
that something is missing
不见了
having to do with Special Agent Dale Cooper
而这东西只有你能找到
and only you can find...
因为这东西跟你的遗产有关
because of something about your heritage.
她就说了这些
That's what she said.
我来了  杜鲁门警长
I'm here, Sheriff Truman.
好  安迪
Good, Andy.
我感觉好点了  杜鲁门警长
I'm feeling a bit better now, Sheriff Truman.
我以为这抱木头的女人精神有问题
I thought that log woman was 10-96
是不允许在这楼里的
and not even allowed in this building.
那是一种口香糖
That's on account of a kind of gum.
我会尝尝的
Well, I'll chew on that.
够了  查德
That's enough, Chad.
她的木头会告诉她信息
She gets messages from her log.
匹诺曹的朋友
Pinocchio's friend.
晚安  查德
Good night, Chad.
我要去跟我的小松果聊聊
I'll go have a word with my pinecone.
劳拉·帕尔默
Laura Palmer?
天啊
Man...
记忆涌现
brings back some memories.
抱歉
Sorry.
这都是些什么
What's all this about?
从玛格丽特·兰特曼到霍克
Message from Margaret Lanterman to Hawk
关于库柏探员的信息
concerning Agent Cooper.
库柏
Cooper?
特工戴尔·库柏
Special Agent Dale Cooper.
我知道是谁
Yeah, I know.
库柏是我父亲生前最后见的一个人
Cooper was the last person to see my father alive.
怎么回事
What's that?
在我父亲去世后几天
Yeah. A few days after my dad died,
我母亲告诉我库柏来过我们家
my mom told me that Cooper had come by the house
跟我父亲聊过
and talked to my dad,
我猜库柏在那之后就很快地离开了小镇
and I guess Cooper left town
我也不清楚
pretty soon after that. I don't--
在那之后就没有人见过或听说过他
Nobody's seen or heard of him since.
第二天  我父亲死于他局里发生的火灾
And my dad died in the fire at his station the next day.
你知道他们的聊天内容吗
And do you know what they talked about?
不  不
Uh, no. No.
我不知道
I have no idea.
有个男人来了
There's a man out front.
他说他叫沃利·白兰度
He says his name is Wally Brando.
沃利  沃利来了
Wally? Wally's here?
他们的儿子
Their son.
他说他想来向你表达敬意
He said he wants to pay his respects to you,
杜鲁门警长
Sheriff Truman.
这孩子
Oh, boy.
杜鲁门警长  看谁来了
Sheriff Truman, look who's here!
是沃利  我们太兴奋了  完全是惊喜啊
It's Wally. We're so excited. He came in unannounced.
很高兴再见到你  沃利
Good to see you again, Wally.
我也是  杜鲁门警长
It's good to see you, too, Sheriff Truman.
你也知道  你的哥哥  哈里·S·杜鲁门
As you know, your brother, Harry S. Truman,
是我的教父
is my godfather.
我听说他生病了
I heard he is ill.
我来是想向我的教父表达敬意的
I came to pay my respects to my godfather
还有向他表达我的祝福
and extend my best wishes for his recovery,
希望他能早日康复
which I hope will be swift and painless.
很荣幸能再次见到你
It's an honor to see you again.
你知道的
You know...
我一直支持你
my heart is always here with you
还有这两个善良的人
and these fine people, my parents,
我深爱着的父母
who I love so dearly.
而且我就在附近
And I was in the area,
我想来关心一下
and I wanted to pay my respects.
谢谢你  沃利
Thank you, Wally.
我来也是先让我父母知道
I also came back to let my parents know,
因为这一直是他们非常担心的问题
because this has been a matter of grave concern for them,
我决定了
that I've decided to let them do what they wish
让他们改造我儿时的房间
with my childhood bedroom.
他们想
They want to--
他们想建个书房
they want to build a study
给他们自己
for the two of them.
多贴心的人
Such sweet people.
这真是个好消息  沃利
That's such beautiful news, Wally.
跟我们说说你都去哪里了  沃利
Tell us where you've been, Wally.
我的家人  我的朋友
My family, my friend...
我在我们这块伟大的土地上
I've crisscrossed this great land of ours
纵横穿越好多次
countless times.
地图已经深深刻在我的心中
I hold the map of it here, in my heart...
和我小时候
next to the joyful memories
在这座美丽的
of the carefree days I spent
双峰镇
as a young boy...
度过的快乐回忆一起
here in your beautiful town of Twin Peaks.
从维吉尼亚州亚历山大
From Alexandria, Virginia,
到加州斯托克顿
to Stockton, California,
我想到路易斯
I think about Lewis
和他的朋友克拉克
and his friend Clark,
第一个看到这里的白种人
the first Caucasians to see this part of the world.
在我的旅途中  他们的足迹
Their footsteps have been the highways and byways
无处不在
of my days on the road.
我和我的影子同行
My shadow is always with me.
有时它在我前头
Sometimes ahead.
有时它跟在我后面
Sometimes behind.
有时在左边
Sometimes to the left.
有时在右边
Sometimes to the right.
除了阴天
Except on cloudy days...
或晚上
or at night.
好
Yes.
沃利
Well, Wally...
很高兴再次见到你
...it's great to see you again.
以及
And...
愿你的车轮驶遍所有道路
...may the road rise up to meet your wheels.
这话说得太好了
That's a lovely turn of phrase.
谢谢
Thank you.
我的佛法就是路
My dharma is the road.
你的佛法
Your dharma...
你
看到
我
对
吗
你
被
骗了
现在
你们
一人
必须
死
道奇
Dougie!
你连衣服都没换
You're not even dressed!
怎么回事
Is something wrong?
什么...
What's go--
上帝啊
Oh, for God's sake.
你到底怎么回事
What is with you?
听好了  梦境编织先生  你去尿尿
Listen, Mr. Dream Weaver, you go potty,
然后赶紧换好衣服
and then let's get you dressed fast.
你比桑尼·吉姆还难缠
You're worse than Sonny Jim.
道奇  你瘦了
Dougie, you've lost weight!
我把这个系好
Let me cinch this up.
这件外套看上去大了两号
And this jacket looks two sizes too big.
昨晚的黑西装看起来很合身
That black suit last night fit you perfectly.
只能带到干洗店
We'll just have to take that to the cleaners
看看能不能换一套
and maybe get you another one.
好吧  你自己系领带
Okay. You do your tie.
我总是打不好
I can never get that right.
我得下楼吃完早饭
Now, I have to go downstairs and finish up breakfast.
快点
Hurry up.
桑尼·吉姆
Sonny Jim!
快点
Get going!
桑尼·吉姆  快下来
Sonny Jim, get down here!
这是你的咖啡
Here's your coffee.
我是道奇的咖啡
咖啡
Coffee.
道奇
Dougie!
你好
Hi!
鹿角镇警局
拒绝访问
需要军方授权
你得来看看这个
You got to see this.
无名死者的指纹查到匹配结果了
We got a hit on the prints we took off the male John Doe.
-他叫什么  -不知道  被隐藏了
- What's the name? - Don't know. It's blocked.
是什么安全问题
Some kind of security issue.
知道是谁隐藏的吗
Well, can you tell who blocked it?
军方
Military.
拒绝访问
需要军方授权
谢谢你们来见我们
Thank you for meeting us.
走吧
Let's get going.
我们根本不在拉什莫尔山附近
We're not anywhere near Mount Rushmore.
我给你带了张照片
I brought a picture for you.
正是他们  艾伯特
There they are, Albert...
用石头做成的脸
faces of stone.
普雷斯顿探员晕车了
Agent Preston gets carsick.
艾伯特
Albert...
我们在南达科他
we're in South Dakota.
哥萨克人在俄罗斯
Cossacks are in Russia.
晕车
Carsick! -
需要靠边停车吗
Do you need me to pull over?
你没睡好吗  艾伯特
Up on the wrong side of bed this morning, Albert?
我们知道些什么
What have we got?
我们是在他的车偏离道路后发现他的
We found him after his car went off the road.
他一直在吐某种毒药
He'd been, uh, throwing up some kind of poison.
一定是在当地吃饭了
Must have eaten locally.
他们现在正在实验室里做分析
They're, uh, analyzing it in the lab.
接触过他呕吐物的高速公路巡警被送往了医院
Exposure to it sent the highway patrolman to the hospital.
正如我所提到的  呕吐物还在实验室中
As I mentioned, the vomit's still in the lab.
这是我们在他的后备箱里找到的
This is what we found in his trunk--
可卡因
cocaine,
机关枪
machine gun,
狗腿
dog leg.
什么  没有奶酪和饼干吗
What, no cheese and crackers?
先替艾伯特道歉
Apologies in advance for Albert.
就是他  对吧
That's your man, right?
苍天啊
Holy jumpin' George.
咱们去和他聊聊
Let's go talk to him.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
我现在要和
I am going to speak now
特工戴尔· 库柏谈一谈
to Special Agent Dale Cooper.
如果需要我们的话  我们就在大厅
We'll be down the hall if you need us.
谢谢  墨菲监狱长
Thank you, Warden Murphy.
很高兴
It's very good
再次见到你  老朋友
to see you again, old friend.
特别  特别高兴再次见到你  老朋友
It's very, very good to see you again, old friend.
我已经很久很久
I haven't seen you
没有见过你
in a long, long time.
你的确很久没见过我了
No, you haven't.
这是事实
This is true.
戈登  我真的  真的很怀念
Gordon, I've really, really missed
我们一起度过的时光
spending time together.
是啊  小库
Yes, Coop.
我也是  很怀念我们一起度过的美好时光
I, too, have missed our good times together.
你这些年都去哪了
Where have you been all these years?
戈登
Gordon,
我做卧底的
I've been working undercover
这么些年
all these years,
主要和我们的同事
working primarily with our colleague
菲利普·杰弗里斯一起工作
Phillip Jeffries.
菲利普·杰弗里斯
Phillip Jeffries?
我得向你
I need to be debriefed by you
汇报一下这次工作  戈登
about this work, Gordon.
我会告诉你整个故事
I will tell you the whole story,
所有的迂回曲折
all its twists and turns,
我本来也正准备这么做
and I was going to do so.
我在向你汇报的路上
I was on my way to present it to you.
比计划日程稍晚了些
I was a little bit behind schedule
当我的车在转向
when my car veered over
冲出了马路
across the road,
发生了事故
and I had my accident.
是的  小库  这也是我们找到你的方式和原因
Yes, Coop. This is how and why we found you.
我要向你汇报  戈登
I need to be debriefed by you, Gordon.
我在向你汇报的路上
I was on my way to present it.
比计划日程稍晚了些
I was a little bit behind schedule
当我的车在转向时冲出了马路
when my car veered over off the road,
发生了事故
and I had my accident.
我留信息了
I've left messages.
什么信息  小库
What messages were those, Coop?
我留了信息  这样菲利普就知道是安全的
Messages so Phillip knows it's safe.
戈登
Gordon?
你准备什么时候把我弄出去
When are you going to get me out of here?
小库  这里的这些同事
Coop, these fine fellows here
现在有足够的理由扣押你
have sufficient cause to hold you for now.
当然  我会在法庭上
Of course, I will be exonerated
被宣判无罪的
in courts of law.
很好  小库
Very good, Coop.
别担心  我们会努力
And rest assured that we are working
带你回家好好聊聊的
to bring you back home for our talk.
我从未真正地离开过家  戈登
I've never really left home, Gordon.
一会见  老朋友
See you soon, old friend.
我们可以再扣押他两天
We can hold him for two more days
也无需提出指控
without filing any charges.
我猜你还没给他打电话
I assume you haven't given him his phone call.
还没
No, we haven't.
墨菲监狱长  我建议你
Warden Murphy, I suggest you give him
私下给他打个电话
his private phone call,
而我想听到整个过程
and I expect to hear all about it.
他没有去费城  他去往西边了
He wasn't going to Philadelphia. He was headed west.
联系过他的几个人
A few people who have come in contact with him
身体都感到不舒服
have gotten physically ill.
你现在觉得还好吗  艾伯特
Are you feeling all right, Albert?
我还好  塔米
I'm fine, Tammy.
谁是菲利普·杰弗里斯
And who is Phillip Jeffries?
他是前任联调局探员
He's a former FBI agent.
你戴着窃听器  塔米
You're wearing a wire, Tammy.
是你叫我戴的
You asked me to.
好吧  去餐厅等着
Right. Go wait in the restaurant.
我现在感觉好多了
I'm feeling better now.
艾伯特  你在监狱里对库柏的反应
Albert, your reaction in prison to Cooper,
我以前从没看到你这样
I've not seen this before.
你有什么事要和我说吗
Is there something you'd like to tell me?
既然你问了
Well, since you asked,
我没法告诉你我有多后悔这事
and I can't tell you how sorry I am about this...
我批准菲利普向库柏透露一些信息
I authorized Phillip to give Cooper some information.
库柏和菲利普吗
Cooper and Phillip?
搞什么
What the hell?
菲利普·杰弗里斯已经失去联系好几年了
Phillip Jeffries has been off the radar for years.
那是很多年前的事了  戈登
This was years ago, Gordon.
他打给我
He called me.
是吗
He did, did he?
我知道  我以为库柏有麻烦
I know. I thought Cooper was in trouble--
至少菲利普是这么说的
at least that's what Phillip said.
紧急  他说
"Urgent," he said.
库柏急需这个信息
Cooper needed this information urgently.
-你和库柏谈了吗  -没
- Did you talk to Cooper? - No.
他们想要什么信息
What information did they want?
我和菲利普说我们的人在哥伦比亚
I told Phillip who our man was in Columbia.
然后呢
And?
一周后  我们的人就被杀了
A week later, that man was killed.
艾伯特
Albert.
我们今天看到的库柏
This business that we witnessed today with Cooper,
我不喜欢
I don't like it.
是的
No.
-事情不对劲  -是的
- Something's wrong. -Yes.
-有可能是意外  但我不这么认为  -是的
- It could be the accident, but I don't think so. -No.
艾伯特  你刚刚用脚在水泥地上弄出的声音
Albert, that sound you just made of your feet on the concrete,
就像是有一把刀在我脑里磨
it's like a knife in my brain.
对不起  戈登
I'm sorry, Gordon.
艾伯特  太响了
Albert, this thing is turned up to the max.
别动了
Please.
对不起  戈登
I'm sorry, Gordon.
我觉得他看到我的反应不对劲
I don't think he greeted me properly,
如果你明白我的意思
if you take my meaning.
是的  不合适
No, he didn't.
事情非常不对劲
Something is very wrong.
是的
Yes.
艾伯特  我很不想承认这点
Albert, I hate to admit this,
但是我完全不明白状况
but I don't understand this situation at all.
是的
No.
你明白状况吗  艾伯特
Do you understand this situation, Albert?
蓝色玫瑰[从未见过的事物]
Blue Rose.
前所未有
It doesn't get any bluer.
艾伯特  在我们采取行动之前
Albert, before we do anything else,
我们需要人去看着库柏
we need one certain person to take a look at Cooper.
我支持你
I'm right with you.
你还知道她住哪吗
Do you still know where she lives?
我知道她在哪喝酒
I know where she drinks.
枪炮酒吧